







Skills

FRONTEND

JavaScript, React.js, Redux, TypeScript, Tailwind, Accessibility, Material-UI, Bootstrap, Context API, D3.js, Mapbox

BACKEND

Node.js, Express.js, Next.js, Spring boot (basic), Fiber (basic)

DATABASES

MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firebase, serverless Netlify

TESTING

Jest, React Testing Library.

DEVOPS

Heroku, Docker, Bash, GitHub Actions

CLOUD

AWS

OTHER LANGUAGES

Java, Python, Go.

AGILE METHODOLOGY

Scrum, Kanban

OTHER

Shopify, Sanity, Wordpress.

Languages

English - Fluent

Finnish - Novice (Learning) Vietnamese - Native

Cuong Vu

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Helsinki, Finland (based in Helsinki, but able to relocate everywhere within Finland or Europe)

Cuong is an up-and-coming Full Stack Developer who has proven his abilities in action. Cuong has already worked in an e-commerce company as well as building websites for customers. In addition to his skill set in web development, Cuong is a recent graduate with a B.B.A. degree in International Business. He has pursuits in marketing, leadership, and social entrepreneurship. This rare blend of backgrounds enables Cuong to understand the business objectives and use cases behind his work as a developer.

Experience

Mehtaheino | Espoo, Finland | July 2022 - October 2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- Developed an e-commerce website project for the firm using React, Node.js, and other Micro service technologies.
- Designed a scaleable web-based application structure and worked with other developers to deliver the web service on time.
- Communicated with UI designer, sales team and content creator for efficient workflow.
- Worked with DevOps practices (Bash scripting, Docker containers, and CI/CD with GitHub Actions) and Cloud Services with AWS.

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | October 2021 - November 2022

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- Sharpening competence as a Full Stack Developer by collaborating with other developers of different seniorities on a diverse range of projects and real-life challenges.
- Focusing on front-end development with JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Redux in addition to other technologies and concepts such as accessibility and animations.
- Building back-end for web-based applications with frameworks such as Node.js and Express.is.
- Covering additional concepts such as API development and documentation, unit testing with Jest, SQL and NoSQL databases, and version control with GitHub.
- Working with DevOps practices (Bash scripting, Docker containers, and CI/CD with GitHub Actions) and Cloud Services with AWS.

Yield Systems | Espoo, Finland | March 2021 - June 2021

FRONTEND TRAINEE



- Collaborated with other team members to ideate and deliver projects on a quarterly basis • Working closely with senior developer to provide a qualified and professional UI
- Applying industrial standard languages such as CSS, React to a internal web application project

redWEB ApS | Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam | January 2020 - July 2020

FRONTEND DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP



- Developed an internal project for the firm using React.js, JavaScript, and other Micro frontend technologies to store learning documents and engage among each other.
- Collaborated with 10 team members including a scrum master and project owner to ideate and deliver projects on a quarterly basis.
- Contributed to the annual income of the company's revenue of €2.5 million euros by delivering internal projects and shadowing lead developers on large projects.

Page: 1/2

Accomplishments

- Participated in Geebiz 2018, a global contest in leadership, cross-cultural communication, social entrepreneurship and international business
- Participated in Junction hackathon 2022 provided by Google in Espoo, Finland, played a role as frontend developer

RECENT PROJECTS

Youtube clone





React.js, Cloudinary, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

Youtube clone website with authentication, upload content, dark/light mode, comment, chat, like/dislike function. Media storage by Cloudinary, and database using mongoDB

E-commerce Store





React.js, Firebase, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, stripe

Ecommerce website which utilizes Stripe for payment service, The main skeleton of state management is Redux

Job Search Application





React.js, JWT, MongoDB, Redux, Heroku, Node.js, Express.js

Job search website with CRUD, authentication, authorization system, and analysis dashboard. This project is a good case to prove my skills with MERN stack. I have followed a good old traditional design convention of MERN to make this website livable.

Booking Application





React.js, JWT, MongoDB, Redux, Heroku, Node.js, Express.js

Booking website with authentication, which allow user to book a room. This project is inspired by Airbnb

Social App





React.js, Firebase, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, stripe

This social app are created by React and Node. Media storage by Firebase, and Database using MongoDB. This project is inspired from Facebook

EDUCATION

B.B.A. IN INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS



LAB University of Applied Sciences | Lappeenranta, Finland | August 2017 - December 2020

FREECODECAMP WEB DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATIONS



freeCodeCamp is a global learning platform community which focus on providing programming lesson; it is one of the greatest places to learn programming online. According to their claims, each certification requires around 300 hours of committed learning; I have earned ten certificates relating Fullstack development as total, which equivalent to over 3000 hours of studying. | January 2018 - December 2021

INTEGRIFY FULLSTACK ACADEMY



Integrify Academy offers Full Stack Development training to junior developers based in Finland that want to boost their technology skills to the next level. | November 2021 - March 2022

UDEMY LEARNING PLATFORM



15+ certificates in programming and counting

Page: 2/2